<contentList date="12/12/2020 17:49">
    <content contentuid="h109173c2g20adg488bg83dfg85bb72e4c61f" version="1">Byregot</content>
	<content contentuid="hb1cb03eeged9bg4442gae57ga7c0f2e5dd47" version="1">The Builder, a god of the arts who commands the element of lightning and is tied to the Fourth Astral Moon. A purveyor of architecture and industry, he is depicted as an ardent smith holding a two-headed hammer, and his symbol is the hand.</content>
	<content contentuid="hc4ecfce9gf145g4649gbd0eg8aff2edfa140" version="1">Rhalgr</content>
	<content contentuid="h84fd3228g9d30g40bcg9499g10b58294b96f" version="1">The Destroyer, breaker of worlds and god of destruction, commands the element of lightning and is tied to the Fourth Umbral Moon. He is depicted as a magus carrying a bronze staff, and his symbol is the streaking meteor.</content>
	<content contentuid="h77a0c7b0g4a6bg48fega24ega7c83acb8ca7" version="1">Azeyma</content>
	<content contentuid="h59eddc22g4335g4298g864bg3260ab505c37" version="1">The Warden, keeper of the sun and goddess of inquiry, commands the element of fire and is tied to the Fifth Astral Moon. She is depicted as a noble lady holding a golden fan, and her symbol is the radiant sun.</content>
	<content contentuid="h113272b6gba02g4b99g8ae0g9309da7ec56a" version="1">Nald'Thal</content>
	<content contentuid="ha3ac9815g6660g460dg8d64g8b9275951400" version="1">The Traders, the single manifestation of twin deities: Nald, keeper of the living, and Thal, keeper of the dead. Gods of commerce, they are together an overseer of transactions and the underworld with power over the element of fire and ties to the Fifth Umbral Moon. Nald'thal is depicted as a discerning merchant holding a balance while symbolized by the the cowry, an ancient shell currency.</content>
	<content contentuid="h440fdb90gc301g43d9g97aag7f1176bd8c5b" version="1">Nophica</content>
	<content contentuid="h5daa82e2gd2c4g48e7g8761g20a9df6b1fb5" version="1">The Matron, tender of soils and harvests and goddess of abundance, commands the element of earth and is tied to the Sixth Astral Moon. She is depicted as a jubilant farmer holding a steel scythe, and her symbol is the spring leaf.</content>
	<content contentuid="h9916aa63ge2fdg461dg8caeg2ededb8c0631" version="1">Althyk</content>
	<content contentuid="h94c2d904ge957g438eg87b6g2010436fd3af" version="1">The Keeper, the surveyor of change and god of space and time, commands the element of earth and is associated with the Sixth Umbral Moon. He is depicted as an austere emperor wielding a mythril greataxe. His symbol is the hourglass.</content>
	<content contentuid="h9821a976gdce7g43dbg9530ge121c3069864" version="1">Halone</content>
	<content contentuid="hee9c3680gb686g4241g8ab0g1ba43639a0ed" version="1">The Fury, mover of glaciers and goddess of war, commands the element of ice and is tied to the First Astral Moon. She is depicted as a relentless warrior holding a bronze greatshield, and her symbol is three spears.</content>
	<content contentuid="he9e0a408gb5f7g4362gb0bdgc2a4b7993bf7" version="1">Menphina</content>
	<content contentuid="h008b6d80gf657g45bag9f33g9917ee52428f" version="1">The Lover, keeper of the once-twin and now-lone moons and the goddess of love, commands the element of ice and is associated with the First Umbral Moon. She is depicted as a maid carrying a round skillet. Her symbol is the full greater moon.</content>
	<content contentuid="h79e904d5gae58g4006g92c7g951be818ba7c" version="1">Thaliak</content>
	<content contentuid="h9c9c9c35g438dg4aa8g94f6g750fec465bd3" version="1">The Scholar, ruler of rivers and wisdom and god of knowledge, commands the element of water and is tied to the Second Astral Moon. He is depicted as a reserved scholar holding an ashen staff, and his symbol is the scroll.</content>
	<content contentuid="hc93c4a12g2322g42ddgad1ag8026fda43469" version="1">Nymeia</content>
	<content contentuid="hc1f55b16gbb76g4dc4g9f76gcb07a2283b00" version="1">The Spinner, the watcher of celestial bodies and goddess of fate, commands the element of water and is associated with the Second Umbral Moon. She is depicted as a weaver donning a white, silken veil. Her symbol is the spinning wheel.</content>
	<content contentuid="h6b4308a9gc5dbg49e7g969cg9ef1ecb18af1" version="1">Llymlaen</content>
	<content contentuid="h09ba25e1g61d5g47dag9f3dg3a3394158da9" version="1">The Navigator, watcher of the seas and goddess of navigation, commands the element of wind and is tied to the Third Astral Moon. She is depicted as a strong fisherwoman holding a long-bladed harpoon, and her symbol is the wave.</content>
	<content contentuid="hc453a0b2g972ag4baag93bbg2a61c1eb1ce5" version="1">Oschon</content>
	<content contentuid="h4f007545g1102g47c0gacbdg80d5f2f12679" version="1">The Wanderer, ruler of the mountains and god of vagrants, commands the element of wind and is associated with the Third Umbral Moon. He is depicted as a carefree ranger wielding a bow of yew. His symbol is the walking stick.</content>
</contentList>
















